question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Luigi is taller than Mario?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Deus Ex (2000) does not feature the World Trade Center because it was destroyed by"
                 " terrorist attacks according to the game&#039;s plot.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;Half-Life&quot; series, &quot;H.E.V&quot; stands for"
                 " &quot;Hazardous Evasiveness Vest&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The names of Tom Nook&#039;s cousins in the Animal Crossing franchise are named"
                 " &quot;Timmy&quot; and &quot;Jimmy&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Valve&#039;s &quot;Portal&quot; and &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchises exist within"
                 " the same in-game universe.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The ghosts in &quot;Pac-Man&quot; and &quot;Ms. Pac-Man&quot; have completely different behavior.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
]
